A film about bravery, courage, heroism and the ultimate sacrifice.
Kajaki is a thriller, war, adventure film directed by Paul Katis.
British soldiers guarding the Kajaki Dam set out to rescue a
three-man team after one of them loses a leg to a landmine.
Tug, played by Mark Stanley.
Snoop, played by Malachi Kirby.
Spud McMellon, played by Ali Cook.
Mark Wright, played by David Elliot.
Jay Davis, played by Paul Luebke.
Stu Hale, played by Benjamin O'Mahony.
Kajaki: The True Story, released in North America as Kilo Two Bravo, is a 2014 British war docu-drama film directed by
Paul Katis in his feature debut, written by Tom Williams, and produced by Katis and Andrew de Lotbiniere.
The plot is based on the Kajaki Dam incident, involving Mark Wright and a small unit of
British soldiers positioned near the Kajaki Dam, in Helmand province, Afghanistan.
The film explores themes of helicopter, army, gun, bravery, afghanistan.
The tone is emotional and intense.